Christopher Miranda

A hard worker and fast learner with excellent work ethic who is pursuing a career in information technology with a specialization in game development and design. In my free time, I am developing skills in 3D modeling and animation with Unity and Blender. As well, I have taken numerous classes in software development that focused on game creation.

Leadership

Boy Scouts of America

Troop 68

September 2007 – December 2016 **Union, New Jersey**

- Achieved Eagle Scout rank by the age of 16 and assisted eight others in their Eagle Scout achievements.
- Revitalized the grounds of a local church over three months by fundraising in my township and organizing eleven other scouts as well as six adults.
- Held multiple leadership positions in my troop over the course of years including: I.E. Trainer, Pack Leader, Assistant Senior Patrol Leader, and Quartermaster.
- Completed the Nation Youth Leadership Training Conference course at the age of 15.

Experience

Village ShopRite

Deli Clerk

May 2019 – Present **Springfield, New Jersey**

- Guided customers through their experience with our service to deliver the utmost satisfaction.
- Presented and tracked necessary inventory, which included following procedures to remediate failed transactions.

Baker

May 2018 - May 2019

- Guided customers through their experience with our service to deliver the utmost satisfaction.
- Helped write and design cakes as well as bake and confirm fully cooked products went to customers.
- Worked in several departments at the request of the assistant store manager to guide said departments on best customer service experience.

Cashier

September 2015-May 2018

- Guided customers through their experience with our service to deliver the utmost satisfaction.
- Maintain aisle cleanliness and organize aisles to allow them to look full and stocked.
- Trained other cashiers about the job and what exactly to do when certain situations arise.
- Received several awards for customer Service from managers.

Executive Assistant

FJ Miranda Corporation

June 2015 – August 2015 Newark, New Jersey

- Processed orders end-to-end while guaranteeing accurate and successful order completion in order to create repeat customers. My logistical process extended from inventory management to delivery.
- Collected and pursued customer invoices, then balanced accounts to ensure the sanity of the business's records.

Skills

Java Microsoft Word Python Microsoft Excel

C# and C++ Microsoft PowerPoint

Education

Information Technology

Game Development and Design New Jersey Institute of Technology September 2017 – Present